<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Lifestyle on Cyber Bae</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/Cyber-Bae/tags/Lifestyle/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Lifestyle on Cyber Bae</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2008–2018, Steve Francia and the Hugo Authors; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2023 05:13:00 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/Cyber-Bae/tags/Lifestyle/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Attention all Scrum Masters: Here&#39;s Why YOU Should Learn Programming!!! </title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/Cyber-Bae/2023/04/attention-all-scrum-masters-heres-why.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2023 05:13:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/Cyber-Bae/2023/04/attention-all-scrum-masters-heres-why.html</guid>
      <description>I find it concerning when people join online forums and discuss how to get a tech job without needing to ever touch code or have a degree in computer science, IT, or any other related field.&#xA;It only serves to make it tougher for those people who don&#39;t possess the diploma, but are serious about gaining experience, to be taken seriously. Eventually, businesses will start sifting through resumes and only consider applicants with relevant degrees from the industry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Achieve Your Goals as a Woman in Tech: 10 Essential Questions to Ask Yourself for Success in the Industry.</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/Cyber-Bae/2023/04/succeeding-as-woman-in-tech.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2023 16:47:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/Cyber-Bae/2023/04/succeeding-as-woman-in-tech.html</guid>
      <description>The tech industry can be daunting, often evoking feelings of insecurity or questioning one&#39;s capacities. This is especially true for women and minorities who may experience even more alienation in this field due to any impolite remarks or animosity they may encounter in their surroundings.&#xA;I strive to maintain a sense of autonomy in my relationships with others, rather than attempt to manipulate their behavior. I focus on how I can manage my own thoughts and actions in response to those around me, rather than try to control their decisions.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
