<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cyber Bae</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/Cyber-Bae/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Cyber Bae</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2008–2018, Steve Francia and the Hugo Authors; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 09:40:00 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/Cyber-Bae/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Why a Strong Email Signature is Vital in Today&#39;s Competitive Job Market</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/Cyber-Bae/2024/01/why-strong-email-signature-is-vital-in.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jan 2024 09:40:00 -0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/Cyber-Bae/2024/01/why-strong-email-signature-is-vital-in.html</guid>
      <description>In today&#39;s market, it&#39;s more essential than ever to stand out. Even highly experienced developers might have trouble landing a job in the current market. With that being said, here are 3 big reasons why having a strong email signature is crucial:&#xA;It showcases your professionalism and attention to detail. Your email is your first impression in the professional world, and it should reflect your brand and uniqueness as an individual.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Benefits of Programming in 2024</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/Cyber-Bae/post/benefits-of-programming-copy-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/Cyber-Bae/post/benefits-of-programming-copy-2/</guid>
      <description>Programming is a valuable skill that can be used in a variety of industries. In 2024, the demand for programmers is expected to continue to grow, making it a great time to start learning how to code.&#xA;Here are some of the benefits of programming in 2024: High demand and good pay: Programmers are in high demand, and they can command high salaries. The median salary for a programmer in the United States is over $100,000 per year.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Attention all Scrum Masters: Here&#39;s Why YOU Should Learn Programming!!! </title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/Cyber-Bae/2023/04/attention-all-scrum-masters-heres-why.html</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Apr 2023 05:13:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/Cyber-Bae/2023/04/attention-all-scrum-masters-heres-why.html</guid>
      <description>I find it concerning when people join online forums and discuss how to get a tech job without needing to ever touch code or have a degree in computer science, IT, or any other related field.&#xA;It only serves to make it tougher for those people who don&#39;t possess the diploma, but are serious about gaining experience, to be taken seriously. Eventually, businesses will start sifting through resumes and only consider applicants with relevant degrees from the industry.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Achieve Your Goals as a Woman in Tech: 10 Essential Questions to Ask Yourself for Success in the Industry.</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/Cyber-Bae/2023/04/succeeding-as-woman-in-tech.html</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Apr 2023 16:47:00 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/Cyber-Bae/2023/04/succeeding-as-woman-in-tech.html</guid>
      <description>The tech industry can be daunting, often evoking feelings of insecurity or questioning one&#39;s capacities. This is especially true for women and minorities who may experience even more alienation in this field due to any impolite remarks or animosity they may encounter in their surroundings.&#xA;I strive to maintain a sense of autonomy in my relationships with others, rather than attempt to manipulate their behavior. I focus on how I can manage my own thoughts and actions in response to those around me, rather than try to control their decisions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/Cyber-Bae/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/Cyber-Bae/about/</guid>
      <description>Empowering the Next Generation of Tech Heroes In the ever-evolving landscape of technology, where innovation thrives and challenges abound, one crucial aspect often lacks diversity: representation. At [Organization Name], we&#39;re on a mission to bridge that gap by empowering women and minorities to embrace the exciting world of cybersecurity and technology.&#xA;Our Vision: Building a More Inclusive Tech Future We believe that everyone, regardless of their background or identity, deserves the opportunity to explore and excel in the tech field.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Fundamentals of Cybersecurity</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/Cyber-Bae/fundamentalsofcybersecurity/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/Cyber-Bae/fundamentalsofcybersecurity/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Blog</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/Cyber-Bae/blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/Cyber-Bae/blog/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
